As winter takes its icy grip, and we head outside into a cold and crisp morning, we might be dreaming of warmer and sunnier days that lie ahead.
当冬天寒气逼人，我们顶着凛冽清新的晨风出门时，心里或许会憧憬着即将到来的温暖艳阳天。
Although, for many, summer might give us the most clement weather, our changing climate might mean that our chilly winter season becomes a thing of the past.
对很多人来说，夏天的天气或许最为宜人，但气候变化可能会让寒冷的冬季成为历史。
So maybe we should enjoy it while we can.
所以，或许我们该趁还能享受冬日，好好珍惜它。
Last year, the World Meteorological Organization found that the Earth continued to endure a period of significant heating, making it one of the three hottest years on record.
去年，世界气象组织发现，地球仍处于显著升温阶段，去年也因此成为有记录以来最热的三个年份之一。
The most notable warmth was in the Siberian Arctic, where temperatures were 5°C above average.
升温现象最明显的区域是西伯利亚北极地区，当地气温比平均值高出了5摄氏度。
The evidence shows that much of this climate warming is driven by human activity.
有证据表明，气候变暖在很大程度上是由人类活动导致的。
With a shift in meteorological conditions, we’re likely to see more record-breaking temperatures, where, in certain places, summers will be scorching hot and winters mild.
随着气象条件的转变，我们可能会迎来更多破纪录的气温，部分地区会出现夏季酷暑难耐、冬季温暖和煦的情况。
This means for some, snowy winters could become a thing of the past.
这意味着对一些地方来说，飘雪的冬天可能会成为历史。
In the UK, a series of projections, based on accelerating global emissions, found that the average coldest day would not drop below freezing point.
在英国，一系列基于全球排放加速增长的预测显示，当地最冷日子的平均气温将不会跌破冰点。
Dr Lizzie Kendon, a senior Met Office scientist, told the BBC: “It could mean the end of sledging, snowmen and snowball fights… the overarching picture is warmer, wetter winters; hotter, drier summers.”
英国气象局资深科学家莉齐·肯顿博士在接受BBC采访时表示：“这可能意味着滑雪橇、堆雪人、打雪仗这些活动将成为历史……总体趋势就是冬季变得更暖更湿，夏季变得更热更干。”
She’s described this as ‘a wake-up call’.
她将这种情况称为一次“警钟”。
Reducing greenhouse gas emissions is the obvious way to slow the rate of change in our climate.
减少温室气体排放是减缓气候变化速度的有效途径。
Some nations are promising to do this, but already we’re experiencing less snowfall and fewer frosty mornings.
一些国家已承诺会采取相关措施，但我们已经在经历降雪量减少、霜冻清晨变少的状况。
And on a bigger scale, glaciers are melting.
从更大范围来看，冰川也在不断消融。
According to modelling by Aberystwyth University in the UK, up to 92% of glaciers in the Alps could be lost by the end of the century due to climate change.
英国阿伯里斯特威斯大学的模型研究显示，到本世纪末，气候变化可能会导致阿尔卑斯山高达92%的冰川消失。
So, if you’re lucky enough to be looking out on a winter wonderland, get outside and make the most of it before it melts.
所以，如果你有幸能看到银装素裹的冬日美景，一定要出门去，在它消融前好好享受这份景致。